{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Multiply:%202x%20(3x²%20-%205x%20-%203)%3F",
      "correct_answer": "6x³-10x²-6x",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "6x³-5x²-6x",
        "6x³-5x-3",
        "6x³-10x²-3x"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "If%202y%20+%205%20=%2013%2C%20what%20is%20the%20value%20of%20y%3F",
      "correct_answer": "4",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2",
        "3",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Solve%20for%20x%20in%20the%20equation%20%2810x%20-%203%29%20=%2027%3B",
      "correct_answer": "3",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "4",
        "5",
        "6"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "If%20x%20-%202%20=%2010%2C%20what%20is%20the%20value%20of%20x%3F",
      "correct_answer": "12",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "8",
        "14",
        "18"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Simplify%20the%20expression%20%283y%20+%204%29%20-%20%282y%20-%203%29%3B",
      "correct_answer": "y%20+%207",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "5y%20+%207",
        "y%20-%201",
        "y%20+%204"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Factorize%20the%20expression%20%282x²%20+%204x%20-%205%29%3B",
      "correct_answer": "(2x%20-%201)(x%20+%205)",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "(2x%20+%201)(x%20-%205)",
        "(x%20+%201)(2x%20-%205)",
        "(x%20-%201)(2x%20+%205)"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "If%204x%20=%2016%2C%20what%20is%20the%20value%20of%20x%3F",
      "correct_answer": "4",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "6",
        "8",
        "10"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Solve%20for%20y%20in%20the%20equation%20%284y%20+%201%29%20=%2013%3B",
      "correct_answer": "3",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "2",
        "4",
        "5"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20value%20of%20%28x%20times%202%29%20plus%203%20if%20x%20=%204%3F",
      "correct_answer": "11",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "14",
        "9",
        "7"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "Math",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "If%20y%20-%203%20=%207%2C%20what%20is%20the%20value%20of%20y%3F",
      "correct_answer": "10",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "8",
        "12",
        "14"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
